# **Muhammad Rafshan FM**

# Graphic Designer / Video Editor



91+9633414792



rafshanfm@gmail.com



Behance

Be https://www.behance.net/rafshanfmc12d https://muhammadrafshan.webs.com/

#### **About Me**

#### Address



Flat No 28, HSR layout, 2nd Avenue,560102



Creative and talented graphic designer with over 10+ years of experience in product & marketing design. Equipped with a strong skillset of UI/UX and motion graphics, I am eager to contribute to creative processes from conception to completion.

#### Work **Experience**

#### 2019 Till Date **BetterPlace**

Bangalore

#### Senior Visual Designer (Marketing & Product)

Ideated and designed marketing content for digital, social and print media

Ensured design consistency across all B2B & B2C brands

Collaborated with marketing and product teams to develop creative concepts for marketing campaigns

# 2017 - 2019

#### Zefo

Bangalore

## UI / Visual Designer (Marketing & Product)

Designed and produced art layouts for visual communication media including website, GDNs, email marketing campaigns, outdoor and other collateral

#### 2015 - 2016 **Ogilvy & Mather**

#### **Graphic Designer**

Worked for two clients - Amazon & Shopclues

Bangalore

Developed various marketing, digital and social collaterals including brochures, infographics, landing pages and social media creatives

Recommended most appropriate design options based on stated marketing goals

#### 2013 - 2015 **BJY Federal inc**

Austin, USA

## Graphic Designer (Marketing & Product)

Primarly worked on mobile UI icons, website banners, mobile banners and ad promotion creatives for digital platforms

#### 2012 - 2013

#### **Dynamicyards**

Trivandrum

#### Junior Graphic Designer

Developed concepts and creative ideas - graphics and layouts, illustrations icons, company logos and website mockups

# **Education** Qualification **Professional** Skill

Post - Graduation Graduation Plus Two Multimedia B-com Commerce

**Higher Secondary** Xplora Design Skool Sims College Ahamedabad, Gujarat Calicut, Kerala Selam, Tamilnadu

# Creative thinking Team player Communication Leadership **Software Adobe Photoshop Skills** Adobe Illustrator Adobe Indesign **Adobe Premiere Adobe Aftereffects** Adobe XD Sketch Figma













Music



Driving



Cricket

